Finally, the debrief, the debrief is always going to show up. On
Sunday and Monday, as you can say, new, new debriefs are open
on Sunday, Monday, the cool part about what this is, it's going
to give you a full track of everything you did over the
week.
And then once you submit all of your stuff, how your gratitude
is inside a body and being in balance, what your focus has
been.
You're going to get a full AI breakdown that's going to have
a memory, a memory of massive proportion. So if you set a
target goal and you continue to skip it, it will feed that
and it will start to call you out on the things that
you're not doing and start to question why you're not doing them
so you
can position yourself. To acknowledge that and make a different action and
a different change. So a debrief is always going to open up
on Sunday and Monday.
You're going to get an email in your inbox saying, hey, your
debrief is open and it's going to be fed off of the
real data that you got from the week before.